<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyTourGuidePune</string>

    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary locations for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary locations for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary locations for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="durvankura_dining_hall">Durvankura Dining Hall</string>
    <string name="sadashiv_peth">Sadashiv Peth</string>
    <string name="fine_dining_restaurant">Fine Dining Restaurant\n\n</string>
    <string name="durvankura_address">Address: Shop No. 1166, Tilak Road, Hatti Ganapati Chowk, Near
        Sahitya Parishad, Sadashiv Peth, Pune, Maharashtra 411030\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="durvankura_contact">Phone:020 2447 4438</string>
    <string name="oaks_1000">1000 Oaks</string>
    <string name="pune_camp">Pune Camp</string>
    <string name="oaks_restaurant">1000 Oaks Restaurant\n\n</string>
    <string name="oaks_address">Address: Near Shahjanand Complex,, 2417, East St, Camp, Pune,
        Maharashtra 411001\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="oaks_contact">Phone:020 2634 3194</string>
    <string name="sukanta_thali">Sukanta Thali</string>
    <string name="deccan_gymkhana">Deccan Gymkhana</string>
    <string name="vegetarian_restaurant">Vegetarian Restaurant\n\n</string>
    <string name="sukanta_address">Address: No. 636, Pulachi Wadi, Deccan Gymkhana, Off J M Road,
        Pune, Maharashtra 411004\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="sukanta_contact">Phone:086987 73875</string>
    <string name="the_westin">The Westin</string>
    <string name="koregaon_park">Koregaon Park</string>
    <string name="the_westin_address">Address: 36/3-B Koregaon Park Annexe, Mundhwa Road, Ghorpadi,
        Pune, Maharashtra 411001\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="the_westin_contact">Phone:020 6721 0000</string>
    <string name="jw_mariott">JW Mariott</string>
    <string name="sbb_road">SB Road</string>
    <string name="jw_hotel">JW Marriott Hotel</string>
    <string name="jw_address">Address: Senapati Bapat Road, Pune, Maharashtra 411053\n\n</string>
    <string name="jw_contact">Phone:020 6683 3333</string>
    <string name="the_o_hotel">The O Hotel</string>
    <string name="the_o_address">Address: N Main Rd, Koregaon Park, Pune, Maharashtra 411001\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="the_o_contact">Phone:020 4001 1000</string>
    <string name="hyatt">Hyatt</string>
    <string name="kalyani_nagar">Kalyani Nagar</string>
    <string name="hyatt_address">Address: Adjacent to Aga Khan Palace, 88, Pune Nagar Rd, Mahindra
        Society, Kalyani Nagar, Pune, 411006\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="hyatt_contact">Phone:020 4141 1234\n</string>
    <string name="royal_orchid_central">Royal Orchid Central</string>
    <string name="royal_orchid_address">Address: Kalyani Nagar, Marisoft Annexe Building, Pune,
        Maharashtra 411014\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="royal_orchid_contact">Phone:020 4000 3000</string>
    <string name="rajiv_gandhi_zoological_park">Rajiv Gandhi Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="katraj">Katraj</string>
    <string name="rajiv_gandhi_park_decription">The Rajiv Gandhi Zoological Park, commonly known as
        the Rajiv Gandhi Zoo, is located in Katraj near the city of Pune in India. It is managed by
        the Pune Municipal Corporation. The 130-acre (53 ha) zoo is divided into three parts: an
        animal orphanage, a snake park, and a zoo, and includes the 42-acre (17 ha) Katraj Lake.
    </string>
    <string name="the_empress_garden">The Empress Garden</string>
    <string name="ghorpadi">Ghorpadi</string>
    <string name="empress_garden_description">The Empress Garden is managed by the
        Agri-Horticultural Society of Western India. The Society has been managing the Empress
        Garden since 1880, with an aim to nurture and preserve flora of the region. The Garden
        covers a sprawling 39 acres, and is home to many rare species of trees and flowers. The
        Society organizes annual flower shows and arranges various programs throughout the year to
        create environmental awareness among people. The well landscaped garden consists of lush
        green lawns, abundant flora and fauna, play area for kids, and a snack shack. The park has a
        quaint stream of water flowing throughout the garden, and is a delight for nature lovers.
    </string>
    <string name="pu_la_deshpande_garden">Pu La Deshpande Garden</string>
    <string name="sinhgad_road">Sinhgad Road</string>
    <string name="pu_la_garden_description">P.L. Deshpande garden is a project initiated by the Pune
        Municipal Corporation. It one of the biggest gardens in Maharashtra. It covers 12 acres of
        land, and is also known as the Japanese Garden. It is located on Sinhgad
        Road,Pune,Maharashtra.
    </string>
    <string name="shaniwarwada">Shaniwarwada</string>
    <string name="shaniwarawada_description">Shaniwarwada (Śanivāravāḍā) is an 18th-century
        fortification in the city of Pune in Maharashtra, India. Built in 1732, it was the seat of
        the Peshwa rulers of the Maratha Empire until 1818, when the Peshwas lost control to the
        East India Company after the Third Anglo-Maratha War.
    </string>
    <string name="sinhgad_fort">Sinhgad Fort</string>
    <string name="sinhgad_description">Sinhgad (The Lion\'s Fort), is a fortress located roughly 30
        kilometres southwest of the city of Pune, India. Previously called Kondhana (Marathi:
        कोंढाणा), the fort has been the site of many important battles, most notably the Battle of
        Sinhagad in 1671.
    </string>
    <string name="rajgad_fort">Rajgad Fort</string>
    <string name="rajgad_description">The highest part of the fort has remains of palaces, water
        cisterns and caves. The main entrance door is known as the Mahadarwaja. This fort is built
        on the hill called Murumbadevi Dongar (Mountain of the Goddess Murumba). Rajgad boasts of
        the highest number of days stayed by Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj on any fort.
    </string>
    <string name="parvati_hill">Parvati Hill</string>
    <string name="parvati_description">For visitors, Parvati hill is also an observation point that
        offers a panoramic view of Pune. It is the second highest point in Pune (after Vetal Hill).
        The hill has 103 steps leading to the top of the hill where the temple is situated. Other
        temples are dedicated to Vitthal and Rukmini, Vishnu, and Kartikeya.
    </string>
    <string name="lal_mahal">Lal Mahal</string>
    <string name="lal_mahal_description">The Lal Mahal (Red Palace) of Pune is one of the most
        famous monuments located in Pune, India. In the year 1630 AD, Shivaji\'s Father Shahaji
        Bhosale, established the Lal Mahal for his wife Jijabai and son.
    </string>
    <string name="aga_khan_palace">Aga Khan Palace</string>
    <string name="aga_khan_palace_description">The Aga Khan Palace is also known as the Gandhi
        National Museum and is a part of the Indian freedom struggle. ... The museum also serves as
        a memorial wherein the remains (samadhi) of Mahatma Gandhi\'s wife, Kasturba Gandhi rest in
        peace. The palace was built in 1892 by Sultan Mohammed Shah, Aga Khan III.
    </string>
    <string name="no_tab">No Tab</string>
    <string name="details_image_resource_id">detailsImageResourceId</string>
    <string name="detais_text">detailsText</string>


</resources>
